const quizArray = [
    {
        question: "1.Who is known as the “King of Pop”? ",
        options: [
            "a) Elvis Presley",
            "b) Michael Jackson",
            "c) Freddie Mercury",
            "d) Prince"
        ],
        correct: "b) Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        question: "2.Who is known as the “Queen of Pop”? ",
        options: [
            "a) Madonna ",
            "b) Lady Gaga ",
            "c) Britney Spears",
            "d) Beyonce "
        ],
        correct: "a) Madonna"
    },
    {
        question: "3.Which instrument has 88 keys? ",
        options: [
            "a) Guitar ",
            "b) Piano",
            "c) Violin",
            "d) Drums"
        ],
        correct: "b) Piano"
    },
    {
        question: "4.What was Madonna’s first top 10 hit?",
        options: [
            "a) Like a Virgin",
            "b) Material Girl",
            "c) Holiday",
            "d) Borderline"
        ],
        correct:  "d) Borderline"
    },
    {
        question: "5.Which instrument is played by striking it with drumsticks?",
        options: [
            "a) Guitar",
            "b) Piano",
            "c) Violin ",
            "d) Drums"
        ],
        correct: "d) Drums"
    },
    {
        question: "6.Which of the following is not a string instrument?",
        options: [
            "a) Violin",
            "b) Cello",
            "c) Trumpet",
            "d) Drums"
        ],
        correct: "c) Trumpet"
    },
    {
        question: "7.Which of the following is not a keyboard instrument?",
        options: [
            "a) Piano",
            "b) Organ",
            "c) Harpsichord",
            "d) Guitar"
        ],
        correct: "d) Guitar"
    },
    {
        question: "8.The country song Jolene was released in 1974 by which artist?",
        options: [
            "a) Dolly Parton",
            "b) Loretta Lynn",
            "c) Tammy Wynette",
            "d) Patsy Cline"
        ],
        correct: "a) Dolly Parton"
    },
    {
        question: "9.Folklore, Red and 1989 are albums by which singer?",
        options: [
            "a) Ariana Grande",
            "b) Taylor Swift",
            "c) Selena Gomez",
            "d) Demi Lovato "
        ],
        correct:  "b) Taylor Swift"
    },
    {
        question: "10.Which of the following is NOT a member of the violin family? ?",
        options: [
            "a) Violin",
            "b) Viola",
            "c) Cello",
            "d) Bassoon"
        ],
        correct:  "d) Bassoon"
    }
];